Guide to the John Tabor Kempe Papers 1678-1782 (bulk 1752-1774) MS 344
New-York Historical Society
- Series 1: Court Case Records, 1678-1778 (bulk 1752-1774), and Undated, 1678-1778 and Undated
  - Subseries 1: Supreme Court of Judicature, Criminal
    - The King vs. Charles Green, John Rundle, and George Dibble: Riot and obstructing survey, 1762-1763 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Trial in Westchester County. The case was first argued before the Council and then appears to have been prosecuted in the Supreme Court of Judicature. Defendants charged with obsturcting a survey and parition of patents beloning to Abraham De Peyster, Anne De Lancey, Lewis Johnson, and Matthew Clarkson. Case includes complaint, depositions, information, and instruction.
    - The King vs. Timothy Green: Counterfeiting, 1767 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The King vs. Joseph Greshould [Greswold] and John Clark, 1767 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Case includes costs.
    - The King vs. Joseph Greswold, 1771-1772 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      See also The King vs. Joseph Greshould and John Clark in Supreme Court Judicature. Case includes costs.
    - The King vs. James Long: Keeping disorderly bawdy house, 1767 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The King vs. James Neill [Niel] alias George Seymour: Murder, 1770 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Case for the murder of Anthony Collins. Presentment on the same sheet as The King vs. Falmouth. Case includes presentment.
    - The King vs. John Bley: Larceny, 1774 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      On same presentment as The King vs. Daniel Hammond in Supreme Court of Judicature.
    - The King vs. Daniel Hammond: Grand larceny, 1774 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The King vs. James Higby [Higbey], Abraham Lent, Peter Johnson, Andrew Mick, John Van Vleck [Jr.], Jonas Schoonover, Lewis Vandewater, Korah Myers, Daniel Hausbrook; Isaac Lent, and Peter Vanderwater: Riot, trespass, and contempt, 1764-1765 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Dutchess County; Subpeona to Sarah Vanderwater. Complaint of Elisabeth [Elizabeth] Clarke [Clark] and William Clarke [Clark]. See also letters to John Tabor Kempe from William Clarkes, December 29, 1764; Elisabeth Clarke dated January 1765; William Humfry, January 7, 1765.
    - The King vs. John Hood, 1766 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Deposition of William Thompson in case against John Hood. The bill against John Hood is on the same bill as The King vs. John Dalton, 1765-1766.
    - The King vs. George Harrison [Harison] et al.: Riot, 1761-1762 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The King vs. Richard Hutchinson: Grand larceny, 1766 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The King vs. John Campbell: Larceny, 1767 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      On the same sheet as The King vs. William Johnson. See list of legal executions dated 1769.
    - The King vs. George Janeway, 1773 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The King vs. Catherine Johnson: Larceny, 1766 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The King vs. William Johnson: Petit larceny, 1767, 1771 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The King vs. Lewis Jones and Martin Still [accomplice]: Passing counterfeit money, 1770 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The King vs. Phoenix Juet [Jewet] and [William Carter]: Grand larceny, 1774 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The King vs. John Keating and William Kennedy: Trading with the enemy, 1762 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The King vs. John Kelly: Burglary, 1764 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      See: Legal executions, 1764.
    - The King vs. George Klock: Intrusion on Crown lands, 1762-1763 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Trial in Albany County. See correspondence from John Tabor Kempe to William Johnson, William Corry, and Governor Monckton. Case includes affidavits, writ, information, minutes of council, list of witnesses, patent extracts, plea, and notes.
    - The King vs. George Klock: Disturbing the peace, 1767-1769 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Trial in Albany County and argued in Council. See John Tabor Kempe to William Johnson dated 18 August, 1767, 19 December, 1768, and 5 May, 1769. Case includes plea, council minutes, draft of information, and notice of trial.
    - The King vs. Frances Malone: Larceny, 1767 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      On the same sheet as The King vs. William Johnson.
    - John Tabor Kempe on behalf of The King vs. Andrew Lardner, 1772 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The King vs. John Lary, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The King vs. Richard Lawrence, Simon Simonson, and Christopher Simonson, 1760 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Richmond County
    - The King vs. Henry Livingston, 1767 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The King vs. James Livingston, 1769 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The King vs. John Livingston, 1754 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The King vs. Richard Locket: Larceny, 1767 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The King vs. Catherine Longworth, 1772 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The King vs. William Love [Lovett] and John Wright: Assault, 1766 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Petition of John Walker.
    - The King vs. Michael Lowrear, 1754 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notice of tiral on the same sheet as and filed with King vs. John Livingst in Supreme Court of Judicature. Case includes notice of trial.
    - The King vs. Nepthali [Napthaly] Hart Meyers, Hayman Meyers, Ashur Meyers, Hayman Levi [Levy], Moses Gomez, Daniel Gomez, and Isaac Gomez: Assault and battery, 1755-1756 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      See also letters from William Smith to William Kempe dated November 23, 1756 and December 3, 1756. Complaint of Solomon Hays [Hay].
    - The King vs. James Whey, 1754 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Notice of trial on the same sheet as and filed with The King vs. John Livingston in Supreme Court Judicature.
    - The King vs. John Henry Lydius [Lidius] [Lydias]: Intrusion on Crown Lands and trespass, 1760-1764 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Trial in Albany County. See additional letters: John Tabor Kempe to Hermanus Schuyler [Sheriff of Albany] dated May 24, 1762; May 27, 1762; May 23, 1763; August 13, 1764; December 31, 1764; and January 21, 1765; John Tabor Kempe to Cadwallader Colden dated March 8, 1762. Case includes breif, notes, copies of patents, affidavits, deps, deed, subpeona, argument, answer, costs, proceedings of council, notice of trial, and report.
    - The King vs. Baltus Lydius: Trespass, contempt, and assault, 1763, 1771-1773 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Case in Albany County. See also The King vs. John Henry Lydius. See letters from Peter Silvester to John Tabor Kempe dated November 30, 1770 and May 20, 1763; Hermanus Schuyler to John Tabor Kempe dated January 17, 1763. Case includes costs and subpeona.
    - The King vs. Nathaniel Cooly: Assaulting a goaler, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      On the same presentment as The King vs. Joseph Murphy.
    - The King vs. Elizabeth Donohough: Pickpocketing, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      On the same presentment as King vs. Joseph Murphy
    - The King vs. Elizabeth McCarthy: Murder, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Charged with murdering her bastard child.
    - The King vs. Eleanor McCarty, alias Ellen McCarty: Larceny, 1767 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. John MacDonall [McDonall]: Larceny, 1757 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. Alexander McDougall [McDougal]: Libel and slander, 1770 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Case includes a brief.
    - The King vs. William McMon et al.: Riot, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. Lawrence McNamara: Burglary, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. Michael McNamara and John McDonald [McDonall]: Assault and attempted murder, 1756 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. Michael McNamarra: Larceny, 1756-1757 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. William Malcom: Perjury, 1767 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. Nathaniel Marston: Larceny, 1762 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. Edward Mathews: Assault and battery, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Assault on Robert Hamilton.
    - The King vs. James Mayne: Assault, battery, and unlawful entering, 1762 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. Samuel Mount: Counterfeiting, 1772 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. Patrick Mulvanie: Assault, 1763 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. Joseph Murphy: Manslaughter, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. William Murray [Murrey]: Assault and battery, 1758 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. David Moore and Samuel Wickham, 1767 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Ulster County
    - The King vs. Michael Nestal: Perjury, 1770 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      See letter from Philip Henning to John Tabor Kempe, dated January 17, 1771.
    - The King vs. Thomas Newton, John Smith, and Francis Boggs: Riot and assault, 1753 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Assault on John MacEnnery.
    - The King vs. John Nobles and Cornelius Bogardus, 1775 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The King vs. Moses Owen: Maladministration as Justice of the Peace, 1764 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. David Provoost: Trespass, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. John Daley [Dailey]: Grand larceny, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      On the same presentment as The King vs. Thomas Rogers and Thomas Smith.
    - The King vs. Thomas Ogle, Thomas McDaniel, and Alexander McDaniel: Assault, 1767 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. Oswego Market: Nuisance, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. Pompey: Grand larceny, 1767 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Pompey, a slave of Anthony Shackerly.
    - The King vs. Elizabeth Phillips: Misdemeanor, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. Henry Pullen: Riot and assault, 1769 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. Thomas Pearson: Murder, 1760 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. William Proctor, 1756 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. William Pitts: Assault, 1765-1766 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. Martin Pendergast [Pendergrass]: Assault and battery, 1762 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Assault on Elizabeth Wright.
    - The King vs. William Rawle, 1761 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. James Reed and Claartje Reed: Assaulting a constable, 1770 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Presentment on the same sheet as The King vs. Falmouth, Supreme Court of Judicature.
    - The King vs. Augustine Reynolds, John Elliot, Aaron Van Norstrandt, Benjamin MacCord, and John Eagles: Trespass and contempt, 1763 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. Hannah Robinson, 1766 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The King vs. Samuel Robinson, Samuel Ashley, and John Horseford, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Trial in Albany County. Case includes a certificate.
    - The King vs. Silas Robinson: Riot, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Albany County
    - The King vs. Joseph Rodman: Assault, 1763 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Case for the assault of Andrew and Mary Barheit. Case includes bond.
    - The King vs. Thomas Rogers and Thomas Smith: Grand larceny, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      On the same presentment as The King vs. John Daley.
    - The King vs. Henry Terbos, 1765 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      See letter from Henry Terbush [Terbos] to John Tabor Kempe, dated November 23, 1769.
    - The King vs. Peter Taylor: Assault, 1761 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Dorothy Tongue: Robbery and assault, 1766 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Honora Travers: Larceny, 1767 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. John Pell: Passing a counterfeit bill, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      On the same presentment as The King vs. John Thorp.
    - The King vs. Abraham Schenk and Stephen Williamson, 1754 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      King's County
    - The King vs. John Thorp: Murder, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Charged for the murder of his wife.
    - The King vs. James Alexander: Counterfeiting, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      On the same presentment as King vs. John Thorp.
    - The King vs. William Territ: Assault and attempted rape, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Assault and attempted rape of Ann Lasshier.
    - The King vs. Anthony Ten Eyck, 1754 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Notice of trial on the same sheet as and filed along with The King vs. John Livingston [Box 1, Folder 7].
    - The King vs. Godfrey Swan: Murder, 1765 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Murder of his three-month old child.
    - The King vs. Josiah Sheater, Anthony Goodspead, and Towser: Murder, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Dutchess County; Murder of George Henry, a Private Sentinal in the 28th Regiment.
    - The King vs. William Seton: Debt, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Moses Sherwood et al.: Maladministration, 1769 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Defendants are city officials charged with neglecting their duties and thus allowing Daniel Crimless, charged with murder, to escape from jail.
    - The King vs. William Steel: Grand larceny, 1770 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. John Stewart and Thomas Everitts [Everit]: Grand larceny, 1767 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Sarah Smith: Grand larceny, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. William Smith: Larceny, 1760 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. David and Elizabeth Smith: Burglary, 1760 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Michael Smith: Passing counterfeit bills, 1766 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Carew Smith: Assault and battery, 1769 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Thomas Bontall Sparrow and Henry Roberts: Debt, 1760 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Adam Smith: Grand and petit larceny, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Two cases; an Adam Smith was executed for Grand Larceny in 1772; see Legal Executions.
    - The King vs. Andrew Darcus: Burglary, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      On the same presentment as The King vs. Adam Smith.
    - The King vs. John Keating: Assault with intent to murder, 1771 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Henry Smith: Assault, 1757 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Ulster County; All documents are probably for the same case.
    - The King vs. Mary Smith: Receiving stolen money, 1761 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Owen Sullivan: Counterfeiting, 1756 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Westchester County; Affidavit of Nehemiah Lyon.
    - The King vs. John Surman [Surnan], 1761 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Affidavit of John Hutton. See also a letter from John Tabor Kempe to Alderman Mesier dated October 14, 1760. The case was sent to the Supreme Court of Judicature from Sessions; see Law Enforcement in Colonial New York.
    - The King vs. Benjamin Strout, John Lasher, John Anthony, Abraham Antony, John King, Joseph Griggs, Abraham Van Dyck, and William Lush: Trespass, 1761 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. George Sullivan: Cancelling a bond, 1771-1773 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      See also a letter from George Sullivan to John Tabor Kempe dated October 23, 1772.
    - The King vs. Solomon Seaman: Assault and battery, 1765-1767 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Dirck Swart: Embracery, 1767-1768 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The King vs. Samuel Smith: Forgery, 1767 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The King vs. Venus: Burglary, 1766 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Venus, slave of Catherine Ball. Depositions of Thomas Dugel [Dugall] and Joseph Forbes.
    - The King vs. Nathaniel Underhill: Usurping office of Mayor, Westchester, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      See also John Hunt vs. Nathaniel Underhill and John Williams.
    - The King vs. Nathaniel Underhill: Presenting counterfeit lottery ticket, 1763-1764 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Case includes indictment and deposition.
    - The King vs. James Van Kleeck, Peter Van Kleeck, and John Russel: Riot and assault, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The King vs. Peter Vandewater: Riot, 1765 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Dutchess County
    - The King vs. Henry Van Ranselaer [Van Renselaer], Jacob Freese, and Stephen Van Dyck: Maladministration as Justice of the Peace, 1765 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Case includes recognition of costs.
    - The King vs. Henry Van Ranselaer, Jacob Freese, Stephen Van Dyck/ Henry Van Reselaer, John Ten Broeck, Samuel Ten Broeck, Hendrick Rowe, and Gabriel Eyselstyne, 1765 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Trial in Albany County. Case includes recognizance for defendants' costs.
    - The King vs. Anthony Van Schaick: Trespass and contempt, 1764 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Albany County and New York City.
    - The King vs. Sybrant Goose Van Schaick and Jacob Fitchet [Titchet], 1759-1764 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The King vs. Godardus Van Solingen, 1767 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The King vs. Johannes Van Zandt [Nehemiah Rossel]: Debt, 1760-1762 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      The case began in Sessions and continued in Supreme Court Judicature against Van Zandt. Notice of trial on the same sheet as and filed with The King vs. George Harrison et al. in Supreme Court Judicature.
    - The King vs. John Van Zandt: Assaulting a constable, 1753 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The King vs. Mathias Vredenburgh, John Lasher, John Stout, Joseph Griggs, Abraham Anthony, John King, and John Anthony: Obstructing the King's highway, 1764 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Case regarding stones on the King's highway.
    - The King vs. Patrick Walsh and John [James] Graham: Assault and battery, 1769 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The King vs. Edward Webb and James Baker: Riot and breaking lamps, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The King vs. Joseph Westbrook, Anthony Van Natta, Abraham Van Acken, and [Richard Gardener], 1754 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      New York City and Sussex County, New Jersey; Also ag. Richard Gardener. Citation: court determined with Goebel and Naughton, Law Enforcement in Colonial New York. IN SCJ NY, defs argued that real jurisdiction was NJ. See Law Enforcement. Boundary dispute.
    - The King vs. Thomas White: Debt, 1763 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      See also The King vs. Waddel Cunningham and Thomas White [trading with the enemy case].
    - The King vs. John Willet: Fraud, 1754 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Case for knowingly shipping bad pork for exportation on sloop Catherine. Notice of trial on same sheet as and filed with The King vs. John Livingston, Supreme Court of Judicature.
    - The King vs. John Willet, 1765 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Queens County; Case involving the blockage of a highway in Queens.
    - The King vs. Marinus Willet and Gilbert Smith: Assault and battery, 1769 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Presentment on same presentmen and filed with The King vs. Mary Daily, Supreme Court of Judicature.
    - The King vs. George Wittmer and John Haumaid: Forgery, 1772 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Case includes presentment.
    - The King vs. John Wright: Sacrilege, 1766-1767 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Theft of a Prayer Book.
    - The King vs. Elizabeth Young [Thomas Jones]: Larceny, 1766 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The King vs. John Van Rensselaer [Van Renselaer]: Intrusion on Crown lands, 1767-1773 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Case later brought before the council. See also correspondence between John Tabor Kempe and David Jones. See also Dirck Swart to James Duane, 6 February, 1769. Case includes report, notes, abstracts of evidence, instructions, information,list of evidences, boundaries, plea, rules, council minutes, notice of trial, and exception.
  - Subseries 2: Supreme Court of Judicature, Civil
    - Richard Collingwood vs. Andrew Seton, 1770 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Case includes notice of bail.
    - John Adam vs. Terence Reilly [Rielly]: Debt, 1774 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Case includes narration, copy of bond, and narrative of affairs of John Watts.
    - Thomas Allen que tam vs. Sugar, 1769 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Case includes draft of judgement roll.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] Jeronomus Alstyne vs. [John Styles] Richard Minifie, Andrew Gauthier, Abraham Van Deursen, and James Van Varck: Ejectment, 1773-1775 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Case includes list of evidence, notice of trial, narr in ejectment, notes on trial, brief, notices, costs, list of witnesses, common rule and plea.
    - Theophilus Anthony vs. John Franklin: Trespass and assault, 1775 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      John Jay attorny for John Franklin and Thomas Cochran to be examined. Case includes Brief, draft notice of trial, replication, draft examining witness, plea, and draft of narration.
    - Gideon Avery vs. Dennis MacGillicuddy [MacGillycuddy]: Assault, 1761-1762 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Affidavits given by Loveit Thurston, Goerge Furman. The plaintiff was a lieut. on the privateer Mars, commanded by MacGillicuddy. Witnesses: Capt. John Hanson, John Lamkein, Michell Sisoholt, Doctor Everatt, and Joseph [?] Thuston [?]. Case includes plea (copy), replication, petition for bail, bail notice, affidavits, brief, notices, demand of plea, and costs.
    - Stacy Beakes vs. Benjamin Doughty: Debt, 1766-1770 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Case includes receipt of bond, notice of bail, narratio (draft), bail bond, and exception against bail.
    - Catherine Benson vs. John Van Zandt: Trespass and debt, 1753-1754 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Case includes writ (copy), bonds (copies), and case notes.
    - Abraham Bloodgood vs. William Duer, 1774 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Trial in Albany County. Case first heard in Albany Mayor's Court. One document states Bloodgood ads. Duer, appears to be an error. Case includes notices of motion for procedendo and copy of affidavit.
    - Nicholas Bogart [Bogert] vs. Abraham Alinor [Allen]: Assault, 1763 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Case includes plea and replication.
    - Benjamin Booth vs. Daniel Blouin, 1772 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Case includes notice of bail and costs.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] Jacob Brewerton and John Johnson vs. [John Stiles] John Dudley: Ejectment, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Trial in Kings County. Case includes narratio, directions for serving declarations of ejectment.
    - John Brinner vs. Andrew Burnes and James Melville, 1766 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Burnes and Melville attempted to hire John Gerratt from Brinner, who may have been Brinner's apprentice. Case includes declaration, statement of case, pleas, statements of cost, notice of trial, and brief.
    - Thomas Brookman vs. Joseph Hallett: Trespass, 1772 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Case includes issue roll.
    - Benjamin Brown vs. Henry Collins, 1772 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Case includes notice to show cause and notes.
    - Charles Oliver Bruff vs. Edward Nicolls [Nicoll] Jr.: Assault and battery, 1767-1770 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Case includes notice of trial, countermand, note, narratio, plea, replication, notice of motion, and costs.
    - Richard Budd vs. Joseph Tomkins: Trespass, assault, and battery, 1770 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Trial took place in New York City and Westchester County. Case includes petitions, order for bail, notices, affidavit, change of venue, briefs, note of evidence, narratio (draft), notes, list of witnesses for plaintiff, and plea.
    - Henry Chase vs. Stephen Case: Trespass, 1770-1771 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Trial in Ulster County. See correspondence between Henry Chase and John Tabor Kempe. See also Stephen Case to John Tabor Kempe, dated 4 July, 1770 and John Nicoll to Kempe, dated 22 September, 1770. Case includes narratio, plea, and statement of case.
    - William Cheslyn vs. John Campbell, 1760 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Court source on John Tabor Kempe's list of sheriff's fees for various cases. Case includes account.
    - Francis Child vs. Guy Johnson, 1775 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Case includes steps of fine, minute, warrants, writ, and precipes.
    - [Peter Quiet ex dem] George Clarke, Peter De Lancey, and others vs. James Breakenridge [Brakenridge], 1770 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Trial in Albany County. Case includes notes and brief.
    - Stanford Cornehill vs. John Bayley: Maladministration as Justice of the Peace, 1755 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Trial in Dutchess County. Case includes draft of affidavit and complaint. Criminal case apparently not pursued.
    - Garret Cosyne vs. Jeremiah Field: Trespass and assault, 1762 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notice of trial on the same sheet as and filed with The King vs. George Harrison et al in Supreme Court Judicature. Case includes trial notes, replication, narratio, notices, costs, petition and order for bail, brief, and plea.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] Daniel Coxe and others vs. [John Stiles] Thomas Skidmore and Abigail Skidmore: Ejectment, 1767 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      The case is on John Tabor Kempe's list of fees for 1767. Case includes docket and issue roll. Docket may be for other Coxe cases.